[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "Hey there! I am Alice. Today, I am here to help you plan your next great travel adventure. But first, let's get to know each other a little! What is your name and how old are you?",
        "user_answer": "Hi, my name is Sofia and I'm 24 years old.",
        "emotion": "neutral"
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Nice to meet you, Sofia. Do you work, study, or a bit of both?",
        "user_answer": "I'm a student.",
        "emotion": "neutral"
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "That's great! I bet that keeps you busy. When you do get some free time, how do you love to spend it? Any favorite hobbies?",
        "user_answer": "I like to play basketball and travel.",
        "emotion": "happy"
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "That sounds like fun! I feel like people's hobbies often influence how they like to travel. When you're on vacation, what's your favorite way to spend your days? Are you more into sightseeing, adventure, relaxation, food, or something else?",
        "user_answer": "I like to relax on a beach with a good book or see some nature.",
        "emotion": "happy"
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "That sounds like the perfect way to spend a trip! And speaking of trips - Who do you like to go with?",
        "user_answer": "I like to travel with my boyfriend.",
        "emotion": "happy"
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Nice! If you had to pick your top 3 favorite trips so far, which ones stand out?",
        "user_answer": "My top three travels were to the USA, South Africa, and Paris.",
        "emotion": "happy"
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "Wow, these sound incredible! What did you enjoy most about each of those trips?",
        "user_answer": "I did a road trip in the USA, which was fun. In South Africa, I got to visit some friends and in Paris, I got to see the Olympic Games.",
        "emotion": "happy"
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "That sounds amazing! On the other hand, is there anything about traveling that you don't enjoy? Or something you don't like doing while traveling?",
        "user_answer": "One thing I try to avoid is the super touristy spots. I'd rather experience the local culture and look for hidden gems.",
        "emotion": "sad"
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Got it! And what's your go-to mode of transportation when you travel? Planes, trains, road trips? Any you prefer to avoid?",
        "user_answer": "I usually travel by plane because I get nauseous in cars, and sometimes trains.",
        "emotion": "sad"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "I'll keep that in mind. Anything else I should know?",
        "user_answer": "No, I think that's it.",
        "emotion": "neutral"
    }
]